todaysmeet.com 2015-03-18

# Privacy Policy - About - TodaysMeet

## Privacy Policy

### INTRODUCTION

Welcome! We work hard to protect your personal information and ensure your information is kept private and secure. The following privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) outlines the types of personal information that TodaysMeet, LLC (“we,” “our,” or “us”) collects when operating the TodaysMeet website todaysmeet.com (“TodaysMeet” or the “Site”). Privacy is important to us. If you have any questions, please send us a note at [privacy@todaysmeet.com](mailto:privacy@todaysmeet.com).

### SUMMARY

We try to collect as little information as possible to provide you with a quality messaging service. Our Privacy Policy describes the treatment of information provided or collected through TodaysMeet. Here are some guiding principles:

  * Information that we collect from you 
    * We collect non-personal information when you use TodaysMeet, such as a nickname for use in a chat room.
    * We collect personal information when you register and use TodaysMeet, such as your email address.
    * Additionally, we collect device-related information, such as your browser and IP address.
  * Why we collect your personal information 
    * We use your personal information to maintain your user account, provide customer service, and enhance your user experience.
    * We use aggregate personal information and non-personal information to improve TodaysMeet and monitor and protect the security of our service.
  * Who we share your personal information with 
    * We do not sell, rent, or trade your personal information with any third parties except​ as provided in this Privacy Policy, with your consent, or as required by law.
  * Your choices as a consumer 
    * In order to maintain a TodaysMeet account we need certain personal information.
    * If you are not comfortable providing the personal information, then our service won’t be useful to you and you can decide to close your account.

### HOW YOU ACCEPT THIS POLICY

When you visit the TodaysMeet website, sign up for an account, create a chatroom, or otherwise provide us with any personal information you consent to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

### INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND WHY

In order to provide you with a high quality service and verify your identity, we collect various types of information when you visit the TodaysMeet website, create a TodaysMeet account, or create a chatroom.

### As a Visitor

We collect various types of anonymous information about visitors to the TodaysMeet website, such as device-related information (device, browser, IP address) and server log information (date and time of day of your visit). We use this information to better understand our visitors and to enhance TodaysMeet.

### As a User

When you choose to create an account, we will also collect certain personal information such as your email address and password. We use this information to validate your identity and improve the quality of the service. You may choose not to provide this information, but will use the Service as a visitor since the user account will not function without it.

Beyond the user account registration process, we may collect various other types of personal information if you use TodaysMeet. We may collect additional personal information if you contact us or otherwise give it to us (e.g., in an email).

### Third Party Services

We collect login credentials for third party social networking accounts such Google Application Services ("Third Party Services") and also use [Stripe](https://stripe.com/) for payment processing related to our Teacher Tools. By authorizing us to connect with a Third Party Service, you authorize us to collect or share certain personal information, such as your name and email address. Your use of these Third Party Services is governed by their Terms of Service and Privacy Policies. We will use and disclose such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### Cookies

We may set and access cookies on your device when using TodaysMeet. Upon visiting the TodaysMeet website, a cookie is sent to your device that uniquely identifies your browser. A “cookie” is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer and stored on your device when you visit a website. You are not required to accept any cookies; however if you reject cookies, some features of TodaysMeet may not function properly if cookies are impaired or disabled.

### Analytics

We use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about the usage of TodaysMeet. Google Analytics collects information such as how often you visit the Site, what pages you visit when you visit the Site, and what other sites you used prior to coming to the Site. We only use the information we get from Google Analytics to improve our Site. Google Analytics only collects the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit TodaysMeet, not your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your computer to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your use of TodaysMeet is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use](http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html) and the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html).

You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to TodaysMeet by disabling cookies on your browser. You can opt out of Google Analytics by installing the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

### HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Your personal information is primarily used for the creation of a TodaysMeet account. We also use your personal information to enhance your user experience, maintain your user account, understand how our service is used, and protect the security of TodaysMeet.

As part of this process, we may aggregate some of your personal information in certain data analysis, and may display this information publicly or provide it to others. When aggregating personal information, we make sure that the information is not identifiable to any particular user.

### WHEN DO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We will never sell, rent, or trade any information that you provide us or share any of your information with any third parties, except as provided below.

We may disclose personal information to school officials when there is a violation of our Terms of Service or in response to service of legal process, such as a court order, summons, subpoenas, or as permitted or required by law when we reasonably believe it is necessary or appropriate to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or violations of our Terms of Service.

We may disclose potentially personally-identifying information to employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations that: (i) need to know your personal information in order to provide services available on TodaysMeet; and (ii) have agreed not to disclose your information to others. Some of these employees, contractors, or affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country. By using TodaysMeet, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.

Information about our users, including personal information, may be disclosed or transferred to entities, now or in the future, affiliated with us or as part of any merger, acquisition, change of control, debt financing, insolvency, bankruptcy or sale of our assets. Such information may be used in the businesses of any entity so receiving it.

### CHILDREN

We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. You cannot sign up for a user account if you’re under 13. If you learn that a child under the age of 13 has created a user account with TodaysMeet or provided us with personally identifiable information, please contact us at [privacy@todaysmeet.com](mailto:privacy@todaysmeet.com).

### YOUR CHOICE AS A USER

Once you have created an account with TodaysMeet, you can access your chat rooms, review the information that is stored, and revise that information. If you have any problems, you may also contact us at [privacy@todaysmeet.com](mailto:privacy@todaysmeet.com).

### PROTECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We employ several physical and electronic safeguards to keep your information safe, including encrypted user passwords and securing all connections with industry standard transport layer security. If you choose to close your account or your account is terminated with us, we will continue to adhere to the privacy policies and practices outlined here.

Even with all these precautions, we cannot fully guarantee against the access, disclosure, alteration, or deletion of data through events such as, but not limited to, hardware or software failure or unauthorized entry or use.

### ONLINE TRACKING

Online tracking is the collection of data about an individual’s Internet activity used to deliver targeted advertisements and for other purposes. TodaysMeet does not track users over time and across third party websites to provide targeted advertising.

### HOW WE RESPOND TO DO NOT TRACK SIGNALS

Customers using certain browsers have the ability to activate a “Do Not Track” signal. Users are not tracked over time and across third party websites to provide targeted advertising and therefore TodaysMeet does not currently respond to the “Do Not Track” signal.

### CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes to the Privacy Policy will be reflected on this page and will become effective immediately upon posting. If the changes are significant, we will do our best to notify you via email or through a notification on the site or mobile application. Please check the effective date below to determine if there have been any changes since you have last reviewed the Privacy Policy.

### YOUR RIGHTS AS A CALIFORNIA RESIDENT

Residents of California have the right to request from us certain information with respect to the types of personal information we share with third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes and the identities of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year. To exercise your rights, you may make one request each year by emailing us at [privacy@todaysmeet.com](mailto:privacy@todaysmeet.com). Your request should specify your full name and the email address you used when submitting personal information to us.

### INTERNATIONAL USERS & VISITORS

TodaysMeet is hosted in the United States. Because the Internet is global, you should note that by providing your personal information as an international visitor or user, you are: (i) permitting the transfer of your personal information to the United States which may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you reside; and (ii) permitting the use of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### QUESTIONS

TodaysMeet, LLC  
Attn: Privacy  
405 8th St  
Brooklyn, NY 11215  

**EFFECTIVE DATE:** December 13, 2014
